EGIDIJUS VILIMAS

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2022

DB Schenker Distribution

river

Drive packages daily to the desired destination. Maintain the vehicle safely and cleanly. Use navigation apps to find the best route. Careful and excellent driving record, high safety standards for large vehicle operation.

2017 - 2018

Nor Tekstil avd. Kristiansand Assistant Production Manager

Efficient management of various daily washing operations, for example: Plan production operations, establish priorities, schedules and workflow for washing processes. Coordinating washing activities to ensure that production and quality meet standards, specifications and requirements.

2016 - 2017

Askaladen, Norge

Carpenter

Skilled at both bench and construction work, mainly with wood and laminate Responsible for new buildings, extensions, maintenance of existing buildings and for all kinds of carpentry Use and maintenance of hand and power tools

2015 - 2016

Clipper Logistics, England Shift team leader

Coordinate make activities to ensure requirements Pick inventory items while using handheld scanning devices Pack items ready for shipping, loading and unloading

PROFILE

Intern-Junior Front-end developer from SØGNE, born 20.06.1992 (31 years) Certificate: Driving license class B Nationality: Lithuanian

I'm very enthusiastic, energetic and eager to contribute to the team's success through hard work.

Attention to detail, good organizational skills and fast learner.

Looking for new opportunities to improve and develop my personal skills.

PROJECTS

https://github.com/evilimas

PORTFOLIO

https://evilimas.netlify.app/

CONTACT

Lohneveien 253, 4642 SØGNE NORWAY

t: +4746555100 e: eg.vilimas@gmail.com





EDUCATION

12.2022 - 03.2023

CodeAcademy - Front-End Web Developer

Throughout the course, I gained extensive knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Sass (scss) and other frontend technologies. I have a passion for creating visually appealing and user-friendly websites and web applications.

1999 - 2011

Kaunas Suzuki Gymnasium - High School

COURSES / CERTIFICATIONS

Current

Scrimba - The Frontend Developer Career Path

Front-End Developer

This career path will turn you into a hireable frontend developer

05.2023 - 07.2023

Coursera - Meta Front-End Developer

Front-End Developer

This 9-course program prepares for an entry-level career as a front-end developer

11.2022 - 3.2023

Udemy - Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS

Front-End Developer

8.2022 - 12.2022

Coursera - Google IT Support

IT Support

Over 5 courses, learn in-demand skills that prepare you for an entry-level job.

9.2022 - 12.2022

Coursera - Google Data Analytics

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

Over 8 courses, gain in-demand skills that prepare you for an entry-level job.

SKILLS

React JavaScript HTML CSS / SCSS-SASS Microsoft Office Suite SQL Linux / Windows

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English Norwegian Lithuanian

REFERENCES

References will be provided upon request